>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 我们已经完成了第 5 行，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: We have
finished executing line 5, and
行刑就会移回来
execution moves back.
现在我们在 14 号线上
Now we're on line 14.
第 14 行如何执行?
How does line 14 execute?
但愿你对这一点有一点自信
Hopefully at this point you're feeling
a little more confident with this
对话。
conversation.
那么第 14 行是如何执行的 ?
So how does line 14 execute?
>> Student : Asks the global scope if it- >> Kyle Simpson: All right so so
&gt;&gt; Student: Asks the global scope if it-
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: All right so
谁在说话
who's talking?
它会成为虚拟机 JavaScript 引擎
It's gonna be the virtual machine,
the JavaScript engine.
他在 14 线上发现了什么
And what did he find on line 14?
我们在 14 线上有什么
What do we have right here on line 14?
>> Student2: 源。
&gt;&gt; Student2: A source.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 我们有一个资料来源，谢谢你。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: We have
a source reference, thank you.
我们有一个大理石的来源
We have a source reference for
a marble called?
>> Studt2: 询问。 >> Kyle Simpson: 询问， so
&gt;&gt; Student2: Ask.
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Ask, so
我们要查的是谁
who are we gonna look that up with?
我们会说的
We're gonna say, hey?
>> Student: 全局作用域。 >> Student2: Red。
&gt;&gt; Student: Global scope.
&gt;&gt; Student2: Red.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 红的范围，全球范围，谢谢你。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Hey red scope,
hey global scope, thank you.
我有个弹珠的标识叫什么
I have an identifier of a marble called?
>> 类: 询问。 >> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 问，谢谢，
&gt;&gt; Class: Ask.
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Ask, thank you,
你知道有个大理石叫什么吗
do you know about a marble called ask?
全球范围的应对将会是什么 ?
And the response from the global
scope is going to be?
>> 类: 是。
&gt;&gt; Class: Yes.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 这是你的红色大理石。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Here's your red marble.
现在我们去那个红色的大理石，那个在记忆中的位置，我们说，哎，
So now we go to that red marble,
that location in memory, and we say, hey,
红色的大理石你有什么
red marble, what do you have in it?
那他有什么
And what does he have?
>> Student2: 问题，问题。
&gt;&gt; Student2: Question, question.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 功能，对吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: The function, right?
他有这个功能
He has the function.
绿色水桶，在第 8 行上宣布的事情。
The green bucket,
the thing that was declared on line 8.
所以现在我们有了一个功能。
So now we have a function.
在第 14 行，小的左右括号执行函数。
And on line 14 that little open close
parenthesis executes the function.
现在执行移至第 9 行。
Now execution moves to line 9.
9 号线没有其他的了
Line 9, there's no more var.
但是我们现在到了最后，我们如何执行第 9 行 ?
But we're getting to the end now,
so how do we execute line 9?
谈话开始怎么样了
How's the conversation start?
>> Student: Hey， green bucket。
&gt;&gt; Student: Hey, green bucket.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 嘿，绿色水桶。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Hey, green bucket.
嘿范围问吧
Hey, scope of ask.
我有什么参考?
I have a what kind of reference?
>> Student2: 排序。 >> Student : 接收。
&gt;&gt; Student2: Sorts.
&gt;&gt; Student: A receiving.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 这是一个目标参考，对吧 ?
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: This is
a target reference, right?
接收也可以。
Receiving is fine too.
我有个接收，或者一个叫标识的目标引用 ?
I have a receiving, or a target
reference for an identifier called?
>> Studt2: 问题。
&gt;&gt; Student2: Question.
>> 类: 问题。 >> Kyle Simpson: Called 问题，
&gt;&gt; Class: Question.
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Called question,
就在 9 号线上
right there on line 9.
我有这个大理石有听过吗
So I have this marble, ever heard of it?
这个范围的答案会是什么呢 ?
And the answer from that
scope is going to be?
嗯。 >> 类: 是。
Yes.
&gt;&gt; Class: Yes.
>Student2: 这是你的大理石。 >> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 这是你的绿色
&gt;&gt; Student2: Here's your marble.
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Here is your green
大理石好吗
marble, okay?
现在我们有了绿色的大理石，我们正在给它分配。
So now we have the green marble and
we are assigning to it.
所以我们不关心现在的情况
So we don't care what's in it right now.
我们去从右边拿到价值
We go and
get the value from the right-hand side,
我们会把记忆和第 9 行的位置
we assign into that location of memory and
line 9 is finished.
现在第 10 行
Now, line 10.
我们记得控制台是如何运作的对吗
We remember how the console works, right?
所以控制台在那里找不到它，就在全球范围内，找到它，
So console doesn't find it there,
it goes to the global scope, finds it,
查找名为 log的方法。
finds a method called log.
但在它可以执行日志之前
But before it can execute log,
一定要搞清楚到底怎么了对吧
it's gotta figure out what's
being passed to it, right?
你可以看到第 10 行，我们正在向它传递一些东西。
You see there on line 10,
that we're passing something into it.
我们要穿什么
And what are we passing?
这是另一个大理石的参考资料
It's a reference to another marble.
所以我们得查一查
So we gotta look that up.
那么这个研究如何进行呢 ?
So how does that look up work?
>> 类: [CROSSTALK] 绿色存储区。
&gt;&gt; Class: [CROSSTALK] the green bucket.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 嘿，绿桶，嘿，问的范围，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Hey,
green bucket, hey, scope of ask,
我有什么参考?
I have a what kind of reference?
>> 类: 源。
&gt;&gt; Class: Source.
>> Kyle Simpson: 源参考，感谢您 ?
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Source reference,
thank you, for?
>> 类: 问题。
&gt;&gt; Class: Question.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 问题，听说过吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Question,
ever heard of it?
答案是吗 ?
And the answer is?
>> 类: 是。
&gt;&gt; Class: Yes.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 这是你的绿色大理石。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Here's your green marble.
现在因为我们不给它分配
And now,
because we're not assigning to it,
现在我们要的是它的价值
now we want the value
that's currently in it.
所以我们去那个内存区。
So we go to that area of memory.
我们把它的价值拉出来，这刚好是一个字符串，为什么呢 ?
We pull the value out, which happens
to be the string, Why in this case?
这一参数被分配给了
And that argument is assigned
to the parameter that
console.log 正在接收，好吗 ?
console.log is receiving, okay?
所以，争论，我们过去的事情，
So arguments, the things that we pass in,
将分配给接收这些参数的参数。
get assigned to the parameters
that receive them.
您可以考虑参数，例如，如果我有函数询问 ( ) 和
You can think about a parameter,
like if I had function ask() and
有一个参数，参数是什么参考?
it took a parameter,
the parameter is what kind of reference?
>> Student: 它就像一个变量名。
&gt;&gt; Student: It's like a variable name.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 它是，但它是什么样的参考呢 ?
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It is, but
what kind of reference is it?
是那个位置
It's that position.
>> 类: 目标。
&gt;&gt; Class: Target.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 这是一个目标。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It's a target.
这是个目标 如果在一个变量中有一个变量
It's a target.
And if you have a variable in an argument
在第 10 行的位置上是什么意思
position like in line 10,
what kind of reference is that?
>> 类: 源。
&gt;&gt; Class: Source.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 这是一个消息来源。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It's a source.
所以 JavaScript 引擎的处理和执行
So there's a processing and
execution of a JavaScript engine,
让你们自己去思考两个阶段的处理
aligning yourselves to think
about two stages of processing.
一个阶段，我们把所有范围，所有桶，所有弹珠都计算出来。
One stage where we figure out all the
scopes, all the buckets, all the marbles.
第二阶段，我们使用所有信息来执行代码。
And the second stage, where we use all
that information to execute the code.
恭喜，我证明您是编译器工程师。
Congratulations, I certify
you as compiler engineers.
您已编译并运行 JavaScript 程序。
You have compiled and
run a JavaScript program.
>> 学生: 嗯。
&gt;&gt; Student: Yeah.
>> 类: [APPLAUSE]
&gt;&gt; Class: [APPLAUSE]